Yes, tension.
はい、テンション
I put it inside.
中にしちゃった
Shall we put it in the camera?
カメラの中に入れてみようか
I want to go a little deeper.
ちょっと奥に行きたいです
limit?
限界?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Can you go?
行ける?
Go to your limits.
限界まで行ってください
It went in quite a bit.
結構入ったね
I might not go again.
もう 行 かないかも
Yeah, is that the limit?
そう、限界かな?
Well then, let's take it slow and get through it.
じゃあ、そこでゆっくり出し切り抜く
Put it in and take it out.
出し入れして
It's okay to just come out and cut it out.
出し切り抜くていいから
Take it out and put it back in.
ちょっと抜いて、また入れて
It's pure white.
真っ白ですよ
This is terrible.
やばいよ
I forgot to mention it for a moment.
ちょっと触れ忘れるよ
It's coming in one by one.
つぼつぼ入ってくるね
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
The folds are amazing.
ヒ ダがすごいもん
It feels the best.
最気持ちいいわけだ
Well then, let's take it out slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり抜いてみようか
Oh my.
あららー
Oh, I came out confused.
あら、戸惑い出てきちゃった
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ